Guide to the University of Chicago Office of the President, Beadle Administration Records 1916-1968
University of Chicago Library
- Series IB: General Files, I-Z
  - Midwest Conference on Graduate Study and research, 1962 (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - Midwest Conference on Industrial Relations, 1962-1963 (Box 217, Folder 2)
  - Midwest Film Festival, 1963 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - Midwest Magazine, media coverage of university, 1965 (Box 217, Folder 4)
  - Midwest Program on Airborne Television Instruction, 1961-1964 (Box 217, Folder 5)
  - Midwest Universities Consortium for International Activities, 1963-1964 (Box 217, Folder 6)
  - Midwestern Universities Research Association (MURA), 1962-1966 (Box 217, Folder 7-11)
  - Midwestern Universities Research Association (MURA), high energy physics program in the nation and the Midwest, 1959-1964 (Box 217, Folder 12)
  - Midwestern Universities Research Association (MURA), high energy physics program in the nation and the Midwest, 1962 (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - Midwestern Universities Research Association (MURA), Ramsey report (PSAC-GAC panel report on high energy accelerators), 1963 (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - Midwestern University Business Officers, 1962-1963 (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - Minnesota, general, 1964 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Minnesota, University of, 1961-1968 (Box 218, Folder 5-10)
  - Minnesota, University of, academic administrators and university goals study, 1965-1966 (Box 218, Folder 11)
  - Minnesota, University of, salary information, 1959-1967 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Misrepresentation, Mexico, this month, 1952-1961 (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Misrepresentations, "Sound Chicago," 1941-1966 (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - Missouri, University of, 1960-1966 (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Mittelbusher and Tourtelot, Architects-Engineers, 1960-1961 (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - Moe, Dr. Henry Allen, 1957-1965 (Box 219, Folder 6)
  - Molecular Biology Institute, proposed, 1961-1963 (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - Mont Pelerin Society, 1961-1968 (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - Moral Re-Armament, 1955-1963 (Box 219, Folder 9)
  - Moreel, Ben, Our Nation's Water Resources, 1961-1965 (Box 219, Folder 10)
  - Morgan Park Academy, 1961 (Box 219, Folder 11)
  - Morgan Park Military Academy, 1961-1966 (Box 219, Folder 12)
  - Morningside Heights, 1961-1962 (Box 219, Folder 13)
  - Morningside Heights area, New York, 1964 (Box 219, Folder 14)
  - Morrison-Washington and Jane Smith home, 1953-1963 (Box 219, Folder 15)
  - Motion Picture Theater, proposed, 1965-1967 (Box 219, Folder 16)
  - Motion pictures filmed at the University, "The Idea," 1963-1967 (Box 220, Folder 1)
  - Motion pictures filmed at the University, "The Quiet War," University of Chicago Cancer Research Foundation, 1965 (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - Mount Sinai Hospital, 1961-1964 (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - Movies, general, 1961 (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - Mundelein College, 1961 (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - Museum of Modern Art, Chicago, proposed, 1961 (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - Museum of Science and Industry, 1960-1963 (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - Museum of Science and Industry, army exhibit on Vietnam, 1968 (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - Museum of Science and Industry, Board of Trustees, 1961-1968 (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - Museum of Science and Industry, use of museum space by the university, 1965 (Box 220, Folder 10)
  - Music, Department of, 1961-1968 (Box 220, Folder 11-15)
  - Musical organizations, Contemporary Players, 1964-1968 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - Musical organizations, University Symphony Orchestra and Chorus, 1962-1968 (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - National, general, 1964-1968 (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - National, 4-H Club, 1964-1966 (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1955-1964 (Box 221, Folder 5-8)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1962-1968 (Box 222, Folder 1-3)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 101st annual meeting, 1964 (Box 222, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Board of Medicine, 1967-1968 (Box 222, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Board of Medicine, meetings, 1968 (Box 222, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences, centennial program and 100th annual meetings, 1963-1964 (Box 222, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences, membership, 1961-1964 (Box 222, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Sciences, membership, 1961-1967 (Box 223, Folder 1-3)
  - National Academy of Sciences, proceedings of the, 1963-1968 (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences, report on "Chemistry in Reaction to Other Physical Sciences" N. H. Nachtrieb, 1963-1964 (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences, 1963-1966 (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1961 (Box 223, Folder 7)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1964-1968 (Box 224, Folder 1-4)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Ad Hoc Science Advisory Committee meeting, Washington, D.C., December 13-14, 1967 (Box 224, Folder 5)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Chicago Industry in Space luncheon, 1965 (Box 224, Folder 6)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Conference on Science and Technology of Space Exploration, 1962 (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, Science Advisory Committee, Ramsey Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 225, Folder 2-4)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, space month, 1963 (Box 225, Folder 5-7)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, space month, 1963 (Box 226, Folder 1-5)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1961-1966 (Box 226, Folder 6)
  - National Association of Broadcasters, 1959-1968 (Box 226, Folder 7)
  - National Association of College Stores, 1955-1966 (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - National Association of College and University Business Officers, 1961-1968 (Box 227, Folder 2-7)
  - National Association for Foreign Student Affairs, 1951-1967 (Box 227, Folder 8)
  - National Association of Physical Plants Administrators of Universities and Colleges, 1962-1966 (Box 227, Folder 9)
  - National Association of Real Estate Boards, 1965 (Box 227, Folder 10)
  - National Association on Standard Medical Vocabulary, 1961-1962 (Box 227, Folder 11)
  - National Association of Student Personnel Administrators, 1964-1966 (Box 227, Folder 12)
  - National Association of Women Deans and Counselors, 1961-1962 (Box 227, Folder 13)
  - National Book Committee, 1962-1965 (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - National Civil Service League, 1956-1963 (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1961-1968 (Box 228, Folder 3-4)
  - National Commission on Accrediting, 1961-1967 (Box 228, Folder 5)
  - National Commission on Community Health Services, 1962-1965 (Box 228, Folder 6)
  - National Commission on New Technological Uses of Copyrighted Works, 1967 (Box 228, Folder 7)
  - National Committee for Progress in Medical Research, 1961 (Box 228, Folder 8)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1963-1965 (Box 228, Folder 9)
  - National Conference on Higher Education, 1963-1965 (Box 228, Folder 10-11)
  - National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, 1962-1964 (Box 228, Folder 12)
  - National Council of Churches of Christ, 1962-1966 (Box 228, Folder 13)
  - National Council on Foundations, 1963-1964 (Box 228, Folder 14)
  - National Council on Philanthropy, 1956-1968 (Box 228, Folder 15)
  - National Council of Teachers of English, 1961-1964 (Box 229, Folder 1)
  - National Council on the Testing of English as a Foreign Language, 1963 (Box 229, Folder 2)
  - National Council of University Research Administrators, 1967 (Box 229, Folder 3)
  - National Defense Education Act, 1961-1968 (Box 229, Folder 4-5)
  - National Defense Education Act, disclaimer affidavit and loyalty oath, the University of Chicago objection, 1961-1966 (Box 229, Folder 6)
  - National Defense Education Act, language and area centers program, 1961-1967 (Box 229, Folder 7)
  - National Defense Education Act, national defense counseling and guidance training institutes, title V, 1962-1964 (Box 229, Folder 8)
  - National Defense Education Act, national defense graduate fellowship program, title IV, 1962-1966 (Box 229, Folder 9-10)
  - National Defense Education Act, national defense graduate fellowship program, title IV, 1965-1968 (Box 230, Folder 1-2)
  - National Defense Education Act, national defense student loan fund, title II, 1963-1968 (Box 230, Folder 3-5)
  - National Defense Education Act and National Science Foundation, criminal penalties provisions, loyalty and subversion clauses, 1966 (Box 230, Folder 6)
  - National Defense Education Act, proposed National Citizens Committee, 1968 (Box 230, Folder 7)
  - National Defense Education Act, title III, 1963-1966 (Box 230, Folder 8)
  - National Defense Education Act, title XI, 1965-1966 (Box 230, Folder 9)
  - National Defense student loan fund, 1961-1962 (Box 230, Folder 10)
  - National Education Association, 1961-1967 (Box 230, Folder 11-12)
  - National Education Association, salary studies, 1961-1965 (Box 230, Folder 13)
  - National Education Association, teacher supply and demand, biennial studies, 1954-1964 (Box 231, Folder 1)
  - National Educational Improvement Act, 1963-1964 (Box 231, Folder 2)
  - National Educational Television and Radio Center, 1961-1966 (Box 231, Folder 3)
  - National Electronics Conference, 1964-1967 (Box 231, Folder 4)
  - National Environmental Health Center in the Midwest, 1964 (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - National Football Foundation and Hall of Fame, 1961-1966 (Box 231, Folder 6)
  - National Fund for Medical Education, 1961-1963 (Box 231, Folder 7)
  - National Health Council, 1961-1962 (Box 231, Folder 8)
  - National Historic Landmark Program, university participation, 1964-1968 (Box 231, Folder 9)
  - National Home Ownership Foundation, proposal, The Honorable Charles H. Percy, 1967-1968 (Box 231, Folder 10)
  - National Industrial Conference, 1961 (Box 231, Folder 11)
  - National Industrial Conference Board, 1964-1966 (Box 231, Folder 12)
  - National Institute of Arts and Humanities, Cultural Development Act, 1962 (Box 231, Folder 13)
  - National Institute for Educational Specialists, 1966 (Box 231, Folder 14)
  - National Institute of Sciences of India, 1968 (Box 231, Folder 15)
  - National Library of Medicine, 1961-1965 (Box 231, Folder 16-17)
  - National Military-Industrial Conference, 1961-1962 (Box 231, Folder 18)
  - National Opinion Research Center, 1961-1967 (Box 231, Folder 19-20)
  - National Opinion Research Center, affiliation agreement, financing, space, 1962-1965 (Box 232, Folder 1-2)
  - National Opinion Research Center, Arthur Anderson Memorandum, 1966-1967 (Box 232, Folder 3)
  - National Opinion Research Center, Faculty Committee to report on university position, 1966-1968 (Box 232, Folder 4-5)
  - National Opinion Research Center, surveys, 1961-1966 (Box 232, Folder 6)
  - National Opinion Research Center, surveys, 1961-1968 (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - National Opinion Research Center, Trustees' meeting, 1963 (Box 233, Folder 2)
  - National Planning Association, 1963 (Box 233, Folder 3)
  - National Repertory Theatre, 1963-1967 (Box 233, Folder 4)
  - National Research Council, 1963-1968 (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - National Research Council, study of post-doctoral appointees, 1966-1967 (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - National Review, 1966 (Box 233, Folder 7)
  - National Scholarship Service and Fund for Negro Students, 1961 (Box 233, Folder 8)
  - National Science Foundation, 1961-1968 (Box 233, Folder 9-13)
  - National Science Foundation, CASE Reporting System, federal questionnaire, 1967-1968 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - National Science Foundation, cost of faculty time devoted to NSF supported research, 1964 (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - National Science Foundation, the Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development United States review exercise, 1962-1963 (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - National Science Foundation, questionnaire on "Research Administration Policies and Practices," 1963 (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - National Science Foundation, study of college and university projected science and engineering physical facility and apparatus needs, 1962-1963 (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - National Science Foundation, University Committee on Proposal to, 1961-1962 (Box 234, Folder 6)
  - National Scientific Data Processing Center, proposed, 1962-1967 (Box 234, Folder 7)
  - National Student Association, 1960-1968 (Box 234, Folder 8-10)
  - National Teacher Corps, authorized in Higher Education Act of 1965, 1966 (Box 234, Folder 11)
  - National Technical Institute for the Deaf, 1965 (Box 234, Folder 12)
  - National Union Catalog, pre-1956 imprints of Library of Congress, University of Chicago proposal to publish, 1964-1967 (Box 234, Folder 13)
  - National University of Cuyo, Argentina, 1962-1967 (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - National University Extension Association, 1963 (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - National Youth Conference on the Atom, 1960-1965 (Box 235, Folder 3-4)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Civilizations, Department of, 1925-1968 (Box 235, Folder 5-6)
  - Nebraska, University of, 1962-1966 (Box 235, Folder 7)
  - Needs, 1961 (Box 235, Folder 8)
  - Needs, five-year plans, 1961-1967 (Box 235, Folder 9)
  - Neighborhood, 47th and Cottage Grove Avenue, Shapiro and Associates, planning evaluation report, 1964-1965 (Box 235, Folder 10)
  - Neighborhood Campaign, Committee to Direct, 1961 (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - Neighborhood campaign, draft of presentation, 1961-1962 (Box 236, Folder 2)
  - Neighborhood Committee, 1964-1967 (Box 236, Folder 3)
  - Neighborhood Committee, general, 1961-1965 (Box 236, Folder 4-6)
  - Neighborhood Committee, minutes, 1961-1962 (Box 236, Folder 7)
  - Neighborhood Committee, minutes and agenda, 1963-1966 (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - Neighborhood financing, Sasaki, Walker and DeMay and Associates, Architects, 1965 (Box 237, Folder 2)
  - Neighborhood funds, program of financing, 1961-1966 (Box 237, Folder 3-5)
  - Neighborhood program, 1961-1967 (Box 237, Folder 6-8)
  - Neighborhood program, financing Cook and Jackson, 5720 Dorchester Avenue property, 1960-1964 (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - Neighborhood, re-use sites, 1961-1966 (Box 238, Folder 2)
  - Neighborhood, university real estate, 1968 (Box 238, Folder 3)
  - Neoplastic Diseases, Registry of, 1966-1967 (Box 238, Folder 4)
  - Nepotism, Committee on, and statement on policy, 1965-1968 (Box 238, Folder 5)
  - Netherlands, 1962-1966 (Box 238, Folder 6)
  - Newcomen Society of the United States, 1964-1966 (Box 238, Folder 7)
  - New Republic, The, 1967 (Box 238, Folder 8)
  - New School for Social Research, 1961-1963 (Box 238, Folder 9)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1963-1967 (Box 238, Folder 10)
  - New York, State University of, 1961-1966 (Box 238, Folder 11-12)
  - New York Times, 1956-1968 (Box 238, Folder 13-15)
  - New York University, 1961-1966 (Box 238, Folder 16-17)
  - New York World's Fair, 1964-1965 (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - Nicaragua, Government of, 1968 (Box 239, Folder 2)
  - Nigeria, 1961-1965 (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - Nigeria, visitors to the university from, 1963-1966 (Box 239, Folder 4)
  - Nixon, the Honorable Richard M., 1958-1968 (Box 239, Folder 5)
  - Nominations, Committee on, meetings, candidates and nominations, 1961-1968 (Box 239, Folder 6)
  - Non-Western Area Programs and Other International Studies, Committee on, and sub-committees, 1961-1966 (Box 239, Folder 7)
  - Non-Western Area Programs and Other International Studies, Committee on, membership, 1961-1963 (Box 239, Folder 8)
  - Non-Western Area Programs and Other International Studies, Committee on, agenda and minutes, 1961-1964 (Box 239, Folder 9)
  - North Carolina State College, 1961, Folders11-12: North Carolina, University of, 1959-1965 (Box 239, Folder 10)
  - North Central Association of Academic Deans, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 13)
  - North Central Association of Colleges and Schools, institutional annual reports, 1960-1968 (Box 239, Folder 14)
  - North Central Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1958-1965 (Box 239, Folder 15)
  - North Central Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1965-1968 (Box 240, Folder 1)
  - North Central Association of Colleges and Universities, Consultant Examiner Conference, Chicago, Palmer House, 1968 (Box 240, Folder 2)
  - North West Hyde Park Area Council, 1960-1968 (Box 240, Folder 3)
  - Northern Illinois University, 1963-1966 (Box 240, Folder 4)
  - Northwestern University, 1961-1967 (Box 240, Folder 5-9)
  - Northwestern University Associates, 1961-1964 (Box 240, Folder 10)
  - Norway, 1964-1968 (Box 240, Folder 11)
  - Notre Dame, University of, 1961-1968 (Box 240, Folder 12-15)
  - Notre Dame, University of, agreement of 1967, Department of Theology and University of Chicago Divinity School, 1967 (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - Nuclear medicine, section on, 1961-1965 (Box 241, Folder 2)
  - Nyasaland, 1963-1964 (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - O-, general, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 4)
  - Oak Ridge, College of, 1964-1966 (Box 241, Folder 5)
  - Oak Ridge Institute of Nuclear Studies, 1961-1965 (Box 241, Folder 6)
  - Oak Ridge Institute of Nuclear Studies, newsletters, 1952-1963 (Box 241, Folder 7)
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1961-1967 (Box 241, Folder 8-9)
  - Oberlin College, 1964-1965 (Box 241, Folder 10)
  - O'Brien, Lawrence F. 1964-1966 (Box 241, Folder 11)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology, Department of, 1962-1966 (Box 241, Folder 12-14)
  - Occidental College, 1962-1965 (Box 241, Folder 15)
  - Officers and administrative salaries and compensation, 1961-1965 (Box 241, Folder 16)
  - Ohio State University, 1961-1966 (Box 242, Folder 1-3)
  - Olsen, Leonard K., personal, 1962-1966 (Box 242, Folder 4-8)
  - Om-, general, 1963-1966 (Box 242, Folder 9)
  - Operations Analysis Laboratory, personnel, 1957-1963 (Box 242, Folder 10)
  - Operations Analysis Laboratory, UNIVAC, 1961-1963 (Box 242, Folder 11)
  - Operations Analysis Laboratory, UNIVAC, installation, 1962 (Box 242, Folder 12)
  - Operations Analysis Laboratory, UNIVAC, report, 1961 (Box 242, Folder 13)
  - Operations Analysis Laboratory, UNIVAC, termination of use and disposition of, 1962-1964 (Box 242, Folder 14)
  - Ophthalmology, Department of, 1966 (Box 242, Folder 15)
  - Oregon, 1961-1962, Folder 17-18: Oregon State System of Higher Education, 1965-1967 (Box 242, Folder 16)
  - Oriental Institute, 1961-1968 (Box 242, Folder 19-23)
  - Oriental Institute, Activities Committee, 1965 (Box 242, Folder 24)
  - Oriental Institute, Aswan High Dam Program, 1961-1966 (Box 243, Folder 1)
  - Oriental Institute, budget and finance, 1963-1964 (Box 243, Folder 2)
  - Oriental Institute, de Buck Egyptological Library purchase from Leiden University, 1964-1965 (Box 243, Folder 3)
  - Oriental Institute, directorship, 1961-1968 (Box 243, Folder 4)
  - Oriental Institute, "The Egyptologists," 1963-1966 (Box 243, Folder 5)
  - Oriental Institute, history, 1947-1962 (Box 243, Folder 6)
  - Oriental Institute, Visiting Committee, 1961-1968 (Box 243, Folder 7-8)
  - Oriental Institute, Wilkie Foundation loan of art objects, 1964-1965 (Box 243, Folder 9)
  - Oriental Institute, Wilson, John Albert, "Signs and Wonders Upon Pharaoh," 1964-1965 (Box 243, Folder 10)
  - Oriental Language and Civilizations, Department of, 1965 (Box 243, Folder 11)
  - Orientation Programs, 1961-1968 (Box 243, Folder 12-13)
  - Organization for Economic Co-operation and Development, Science Committees, 1962-1964 (Box 243, Folder 14)
  - Organization for Tropical Studies, university membership, 1968 (Box 243, Folder 15)
  - Orthogenic School, 1961-1967 (Box 244, Folder 1-2)
  - Orthogenic School, Sonia Shankman Day Care Center, 1967 (Box 244, Folder 3)
  - Overhead, 1946-1964 (Box 244, Folder 4)
  - Overhead, principles for determining, committees for ACE, AAU and NFCUBO, 1960-1961 (Box 244, Folder 5)
  - Overhead, principles for determining, government contracts, 1948-1961 (Box 244, Folder 6-7)
  - Overhead, principles for determining, government contracts, Bureau of Budget, 1962-1964 (Box 244, Folder 8-9)
  - Owl and Serpent, 1961-1968 (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - P-, general, 1963 (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - Pacific Science Center Foundation, 1965 (Box 245, Folder 3)
  - Pakistan, visitors to the university from, 1962-1967 (Box 245, Folder 4)
  - Paleozoology, Committee on, 1961-1964 (Box 245, Folder 5)
  - Pan-American, general, 1962-1966 (Box 245, Folder 6)
  - Pardridge, William D., 1957-1965 (Box 245, Folder 7)
  - Park Forest College, 1962-1963 (Box 245, Folder 8)
  - Parking, 1961-1968 (Box 245, Folder 9-13)
  - Particle, a journal, 1961-1964 (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Passavant Memorial Hospital, 1961-1967 (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - Patent policy, 1961-1968 (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Patents, 1961-1966 (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Patents, Research Corporation patent development, 1961-1968 (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - Patents of the University of Chicago, Benfield, Barnhart, Orland, 1958-1967 (Box 246, Folder 6)
  - Patents of the University of Chicago, Jensen, 1956-1967 (Box 246, Folder 7)
  - Patents of the University of Chicago, Lorincz, 1961 (Box 246, Folder 8)
  - Pathology, Department of, 1957-1968 (Box 246, Folder 9-10)
  - Pediatrics, Department of, 1961-1966 (Box 246, Folder 11-12)
  - Pennsylvania, University of, 1961-1963 (Box 246, Folder 13)
  - Pennsylvania, University of, bicentennial observance of School of Medicine and beginning of medical education in the United States, 1964 (Box 246, Folder 14)
  - People to People, 1962-1967 (Box 246, Folder 15)
  - Pergamon Press, 1961-1962 (Box 247, Folder 1)
  - Personnel, 1961-1968 (Box 247, Folder 2-6)
  - Personnel, employment of more than one member of a family, 1962 (Box 247, Folder 7)
  - Personnel, Fair Labor Standards Act, application to University, 1966-1968 (Box 247, Folder 8)
  - Personnel, notices, 1961-1967 (Box 247, Folder 9)
  - Personnel, nurses, 1961-1965 (Box 247, Folder 10)
  - Personnel, professional staff, 1961-1967 (Box 247, Folder 11)
  - Personnel, wage rates, 1962-1965 (Box 247, Folder 12)
  - Pharmaceutical Manufactures Association, 1961-1966 (Box 247, Folder 13-14)
  - Pharmaceutical and Physiological Sciences, Physiology, Department of the, annual reports, 1960-1967 (Box 247, Folder 15)
  - Pharmacology, Department of, 1961-1968 (Box 247, Folder 16-17)
  - Pharmacology, Department of, Toxicity Laboratory, 1964-1968 (Box 248, Folder 1)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1961-1963 (Box 248, Folder 2)
  - Philosophy, Department of, 1961-1968 (Box 248, Folder 3-5)
  - Philosophy, Department of, space, 1966 (Box 248, Folder 6)
  - Phoenix, 1964-1965 (Box 248, Folder 7)
  - Photographic service on campus, 1964-1966 (Box 248, Folder 8)
  - Physical Education, 1962-1963 (Box 248, Folder 9)
  - Physical Education and Athletics, Department of, 1961-1962 (Box 248, Folder 10)
  - Physical Education and Athletics, Department of, faculty, Stagg, Amos Alonz birthday anniversary, one hundredth, 1961-1962 (Box 248, Folder 11)
  - Physical Education and Athletics, Department of, faculty, Stagg, Amos Alonz birthday anniversaries, 1952-1964 (Box 248, Folder 12)
  - Physical Education, Department of, 1961-1966 (Box 248, Folder 13-15)
  - Physical Education, Department of, 1967-1968 (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - Physical Education, Department of, Racquet Courts, 1961-1968 (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - Physical Education, Department of, space and facilities, 1961-1968 (Box 249, Folder 3-5)
  - Physical Plant, Department for the, custodial, janitorial services, 1967-1968 (Box 249, Folder 6)
  - Physical Sciences, Division of the, 1960-1965 (Box 249, Folder 7-9)
  - Physical Sciences, Division of the, 1966-1968 (Box 250, Folder 1-2)
  - Physical Sciences, Division of the, central shop, 1961-1967 (Box 250, Folder 3)
  - Physical Sciences, Division of the, Faculty Board, 1961-1967 (Box 250, Folder 4)